Linda LaMacchia collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Linda LaMacchia collection 1985-2017
AFC 2017/049
LaMacchia, Linda
approximately 5,302 items
17 containers
3.2 linear feet
113 text files: digital, wpd, doc, xml, edt, let, eps
115 sound cassettes (microcassette): analog
14 sound cassettes: analog
5 sound cassettes (DAT): digital
135 audio files: digital, wav, mp3, aiff
126 moving image files: digital, vob, ifo, mp4, mov, prproj, wmv
211 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35mm
328 photographs: film negatives, color; 35mm
664 photographs: color transparencies; 35mm
170 photographs: prints, black and white; various sizes
126 photographs: prints, color; various sizes
5 photographs: contact sheets, black and white; various sizes
10 photographs: contact sheets, color; various sizes
424 still image files: digital, jpg
40 optical discs: digital; 4 3/4 in.
7 floppy disks: digital; 3.5 in.
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of field documentation, including photographs, field notes, video footage, and recordings of songs and interviews, collected by Linda LaMacchia during her research on Buddhist nuns (jomos) in the Kinnaur district of Northwest, India from 1991 to 2017. Audio recordings include interviews with jomos and lamas about their life stories, and religious songs and chants.
Provenance
Donated by the Linda LaMacchia estate; September 2017 and June 2018.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Access and Restrictions
The Linda LaMacchia collection is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Biographical Note
Linda LaMacchia was born in 1944 in Washington, D.C. As the daughter of a Foreign Service Officer, LaMacchia traveled extensively and lived for a period in Harare, Zimbabwe, and Nairobi, Kenya, while she was a child. LaMacchia earned a bachelor of arts in Political Science from Swarthmore College and attended the Sorbonne in Paris, France, for a year. After college she joined the Peace Corps where she taught English in Tunis, Tunisia, for two years. After the Peace Corps, LaMacchia lived in Blaubeuren, Germany for a year, studying German at the Goethe Institute. She returned to the United States and received a master of arts in comparative literature from the University of Michigan, Ann Arbor and a certificate in teaching English as a second language from the University of California, Los Angeles. She briefly taught English and French in Los Angeles, Boston, and Washington, D.C.
After her graduation from Swarthmore, LaMacchia frequently traveled to India to visit a college friend. As a result of her personal travels to India, her interest in Indian culture grew and she began her research on Buddhist nuns living in Kinnaur, near the Tibetan border. In the late 1980s, LaMacchia continued her education, pursuing a PhD in South Asian Studies and Anthropology at the University of Wisconsin, Madison. During this period, she traveled to India frequently, staying at the Tibetan Library in Dharamsala, traveling to villages across the Kinnaur district and collecting the songs and life stories of Buddhist nuns in Hindi, Tibetan, Kinnauri, and English. Upon the completion of her dissertation in 2001, LaMacchia spent a year in India teaching Buddhist culture and Hindi at Antioch College's Education Abroad Program. She also taught courses on South Asian languages, religions, and cultures at DePaul University, Loyola University, American University, and the University of Maryland's University College.
LaMacchia's book Songs and Lives of the Jomo (Nuns) of Kinnaur, Northwest, India, based on her dissertation work, was published in 2008. After the completion of her book, she continued to travel to India frequently to conduct research and collect more songs and life narratives from Buddhist nuns. She continued as an active member of the academic community, publishing papers and presenting at conferences. While in India, she also adopted a dog, named Puppy Durga, who features in many of her photographs and journals. At the time of her death she was working on a memoir about her time with Puppy Durga entitled Travels with Puppy. LaMacchia died in 2017, in Dharamsala, India.
Scope and Content
The collection documents Linda LaMacchia's travels in India and fieldwork in the Kinnaur district in the state of Himachal Pradesh in Northwest India from 1985 to 2017. For fifteen months in 1995 and 1996, LaMacchia conducted doctoral research for a degree in South Asian Studies from the University of Wisconsin, Madison. During this period she recorded the life stories, songs, and local religious practices of Buddhist nuns, or jomos, in the Kinnaur district. Following the completion of her dissertation, and later her book The Songs and Lives of the Jomo (Nuns) of Kinnaur, Northwest India based on this research, LaMacchia continued her work with the jomos and lamas of the Kinnaur district, taking repeated trips to India between 1998 and 2017 to continue collecting songs and life stories.
The collection contains life stories of jomos belonging to three Buddhist sects: Drukpa Kagyu, Gelug, and Nyingma. LaMacchia also collected songs performed by the jomos, including Tibetan language songs (mgurma) and Kinnauri language songs (githang). The collection includes photographs and video footage of jomos, lamas, Buddhist religious rituals, and the Himalayan Mountains of the Kinnaur district. LaMacchia's journals with extensive field notes documenting her fifteen months of dissertation work are also retained in the collection. The majority of materials were transcribed in Tibetan or Hindi and translated into English by LaMacchia. Materials in Kinnauri, which has no written language, were transcribed into Hindi by Ramesh Chandra Negi and then translated into English by LaMacchia. The collection includes many drafts and iterations of translations in various languages. Collection material and folder headings may contain variable spellings and other discrepancies as names and phrases went through multiple rounds of translation and were transliterated by LaMacchia from Devanagari or Tibetan scripts to the Latin alphabet.
Arrangement
The Linda LaMacchia collection is organized in three series:
Series 1: Fieldwork in Northwest India, 1990-2016
Series 2: Academic files, 1988-2017
Series 3: Personal travel to India, 1985-1990
Wherever possible, Sara Ludewig paired transcripts with their related sound recordings.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
LaMacchia, Linda; Negī, Rameśacandra
Subjects
Buddhist chants--India--Kinnaur.; Buddhist chants--Tibet region.; Buddhist monasticism and religious orders for women--India--Kinnaur.; Buddhist nuns--Conduct of life.; Buddhist nuns--India--Kinnaur--Religious life.; Buddhist sects--India.; Songs, Tibetan--India.; Songs--India--Kinnaur.; Women--India--Religious life.
Places
Kinnaur (India), event place.
Form/Genre
Chants.; Correspondence.; Digital photographs--Color--2000-2010.; Field notes.; Interviews.; Oral histories.; Photographs.; Photographs.; Songs.; Sound recordings.; Video recordings.
Container List
- Series 1: Fieldwork in Northwest India
  - Subseries 1: Dissertation fieldwork
    Interviews, songs, field note journals, and photographs collected during LaMacchia's dissertation fieldwork in the Kinnaur district of Northwest, India. This fieldwork resulted in LaMacchia's 2001 dissertation: Women's Religious Expression in Tibetan Buddhism: Songs and Lives of the Jomo (Nuns) of Kinnaur, Northwest India. This research was also the basis for her 2008 book: Songs and Lives of the Jomo (Nuns) of Kinnaur, Northwest India. See Appendix A for a list of interview subjects.
    Sara Ludewig paired songs and interviews with their transcripts wherever possible. She paired these materials based on description provided by LaMacchia, not by listening to the tapes. As a result, errors and discrepancies may exist.
    - Songs
      - Bure Gompa song, July 1996
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/1)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR065; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Chango Boy by Tsultrim Angmo, Manali, 1A, October 20, 1995
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/2)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR116; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - From a Moorang lama's notebook: mgurma II, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Ga Rinpoche's mgurma (sung in Tokto by Bogti), July 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Githang CD #1, undated, afc2017049_dc62; Track list: 1, Negi Lama (short); 2, Lotsa Rinpoche (short); 3, Song of Separation; 4, Lotsa Rinpoche (Kanum); 5, Song of Friends (Kanum); 6, Nyina Zangmo (Hargo); 7, Chango Boy (Chango); 8, Song of Lochen Rinpoche's Wife (Chango).; 8 audio files (wav)
      - Githang CD #2, undated, afc2017049_dc63; Track list: 1, Yulgyal Tulku; 2, Buddha Shakyamuni; 3, Impermanence; 4, Impermanence; 5, Lobon Rinpoche; 6, Song of Lippa; 7, Negi Lama (long); 8, Song of Bure Gompa; 9, Song of Bure Gompa.; 9 audio files (wav)
      - Githang CD #4, undated, afc2017049_dc66; Track list: 1-2, Tsering Lhamo, Lotsa Rinpoche; 3, Tsering Lhamo, Song of Rest Guru; 4, Tsering Lhamo (version 1), Song of Root Guru (version 2).; 4 audio files (wav)
      - Manuscript material accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc62, afc2017049_dc63, and afc2017049_dc66, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/8)
      - "I'm on the Path," Jacinta Foale, Tso Pema, undated, AFC 2017/049: SR019; 1 sound cassette
      - Kinnauri disc #1, undated, afc2017049_dc25; Track list: 1, Song of Bure Temple sung by Chosem Dolma at Bure; 2, Track 1 continued; 3, Song of Kangyur Rinpoche sung by Tsering Lhamo at Ribba; 4, Song of Yulgyal Tulku sung by Yangchen Dolma (Panwi) at Gautam Nagar; 5, Song of Negi Rinpoche 1 sung by Jamyang Choeling nuns at McLeod Ganj; 6 Song of Negi Rinpoche 2 sung by Chosem Dolma at Bure; 7, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche 1 sung by Jamyang Choeling nuns at McLeod Ganj; 8, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche 2 sung by Tsering Lhamo at Ribba; 9: Song of Impermanence sung by Yangchen Dolma (Nichar) at Nichar.; 9 audio files (wav)
      - Kinnauri disc #2, undated, afc2017049_dc26; Track list: 1, Ga Rinpoche's mgurma sung by Bogti and disciples at Tokto; 2, Lama Topgyal's mgurma sung by Ani Dolma at Pangaon; 3, Sung-gur 1 sung by Hirmal at Lippa; 4, Song of Nyima Zangmor sung by Tenzin Choeden (Chango) at Pangaon; 5, Suffering of Separation sung by Tenzin Kinzum at Jamyang Choeling New Land, Garo; 6, Song of Lobon Rinpoche sung by Bogti's disciple and niece (Gedun Zangmo and Thinley Dolma) at Tokto; 7, Song of Lippa Village sung by Lobsang Dolma at Lippa; 8, Sung-gur 3 sung by Hirmal at Lippa.; 8 audio files (wav)
      - Manuscript materials accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc25 and afc2017049_dc26, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/1)
      - Kinnauri disc #3 githang and mgurma, 1995-1996, afc2017049_dc30; Track list: Githang: 1, Song of Buddha Shakyamuni sung by Yangchen Dolma (of Panwi) and Kunzig Palmo (of Nesang) at Guatam Nagar (Wangtu); 2, Song about friends sung by Tenzin Nangsal, Thupten Choezing, and Tenzin Tsomo (all of Kanam) at McLeod Ganj (Dharamsala); 3, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (Kanam version) sung by Tenzin Nangsal, Thupten Choezing, and Tenzin Tsomo (all of Kanam) at McLeod Ganj (Dharamsala); 4, Song of the Root Guru sung by Tsering Lhamo at Ribba. Mgurma: 5, Negi Rinpoche's mgurma sung by six nuns of Jamyang Choeling nunnery at McLeod Ganj (Dharamsala); 6, Sung-gur 2 sung by Hirmal Dungkyid and Chozing Palmo at Lippa; 7, Sung-gur from a Moorang lama's notebook sung by Hirmal Dungkyid at Lippa; 8, Negi Rinpoche's mgurma sung by Tenzin Dolma (of Chango) at Pangaon monastery (at Sola Mil near Manali).; 8 audio files (wav)
      - Kinnauri disc #3 githang and mgurma, 1995-1996, afc2017049_dc34; Track list: Githang: 1, Song of Buddha Shakyamuni recorded in Guatam Nagar (Wangtu); 2, Song about friends recorded in McLeod Ganj (Dharamsala); 3, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche recorded in McLeod Ganj (Dharamasala); 4, Song of the Root Guru recorded in Ribba. Mgurma: 5, Negi Rinpoche's mgurma recorded in McLeod Ganj (Dharamasala); 6, Sung-gur recorded in Lippa; 7, Sung-gur from a Moorang lama's notebook recorded in Lippa; 8, Negi Rinpoche's mgurma recorded in Pangaon monastery (at Sola Mi).; 8 audio files (mp3), 1 text file (xml)
      - Manuscript material accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc30 and afc2017049_dc34, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/4)
      - Kinnauri disc #4 audio part 1 Tsering Lhamo, June 1996, afc2017049_dc27; Track list: 1, Song of the Root Guru; 2, Song of Kangyur Rinpoche (part 1 of 2); 3, Song of Kangyur Rinpoche (part 2 of 2); 4, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (part 1 of 2); 5, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (part 2 of 2).; 3 audio files (wav)
      - Kinnauri disc #4 audio part 2 Tsering Lhamo, June 1996, afc2017049_dc31; 2 audio files (wav)
      - Kinnauri disc #4 Tsering Lhamo, June 1996, afc2017049_dc36; Track list: 1, Song of the Root Guru; 2, Song of Kangyur Rinpoche (part 1 of 2); 3, Song of Kangyur Rinpoche (part 2 of 2); 4, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (part 1 of 2); 5, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (part 2 of 2).; 5 audio files (mp3), 1 text file (xml)
      - Manuscript materials accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc27, afc2017049_dc31, and afc2017049_dc36, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/2)
      - Kinnauri nuns disc 1, undated, afc2017049_dc32; Track list: 1, Song of Bure Temple part 1; 2, Song of Bure Temple part 2; 3, Song of Kangyur Rinpoche (excerpt); 4, Song of Yulgyal Tulku; 5, Song of Negi Rinpoche, version 1; 6, Song of Negi Rinpoche, version 2; 7, Song of Lotsa Rinchen Zangbo, version 1; 8, Song of Lotsa Rinchen Zangbo, version 2; 9, Song on Impermanence.; 9 audio files (wav); Disc created to accompany LaMacchia's dissertation.
      - Kinnauri nuns disc 2, undated, afc2017049_dc33; Track list: 1, Ga Rinpoche's mgurma; 2, Lama Topgyal's mgurma; 3, Sung-gur I; 4, Song of Nyima Zangmo; 5, Suffering of Separation; 6, Song of Lobon Rinpoche; 7, Song of Lippa; 8, Sung-gur III.; 8 audio files (wav); Disc created to accompany LaMacchia's dissertation.
      - Manuscript material accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc32 and afc2017049_dc33, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/5)
      - Kinnaur songs [notebook], September 21, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Linda LaMacchia #1, 1995-1996, AFC 2017/049: SR024; Kinnauri nun's songs in Kinnauri language, taped in 1995-1996; re-recorded January 29, 1999.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Linda LaMacchia #2, 1995-1996, AFC 2017/049: SR025; Kinnauri nun's songs in Kinnauri language, taped in 1995-1996; re-recorded January 29, 1999.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Linda LaMacchia #3, 1995-1996, AFC 2017/049: SR026; Kinnauri nun's songs in Kinnauri language, taped in 1995-1996; re-recorded January 29, 1999.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Linda LaMacchia #4, 1995-1996, AFC 2017/049: SR027; Kinnauri nun's songs in Kinnauri language, taped in 1995-1996; re-recorded January 29, 1999.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Linda LaMacchia #5, 1995-1996, AFC 2017/049: SR028; Kinnauri nun's songs in Kinnauri language, taped in 1995-1996; re-recorded January 29, 1999.; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - Lotsa Rinpoche song (Kanam), April 2, 1996
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/6)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR062 (Side B); 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Lotsa Rinpoche song (Ribba: Tsering Lhamo), June 16, 1996
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/7)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR007 (Side B), SR056, SR014; 2 sound cassettes; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Mgurma CD #3a, undated, afc2017049_dc64; Track list: 1, Ga Rinpoche's mgurma; 2-4, Three sung-gur by Hirmal; 5, Mgurma from Moorang lama's notebook; 6, Negi Rinpoche's mgurma; 7, Mgurma sung by Manali; 8-9, Sorang Lama's mgurma.; 9 audio files (wav)
      - Mgurma CD #4a, undated, afc2017049_dc67; Track list: 1, Ani Dolma's mgurma; 2, Negi's mgurma; 3, Sol Deps; 4, Kadeen and Sawai lama; 5, Khada Hosal; 6, Nesang; 7, Nesang Tashijong; 8, Tila Wangju.; 8 audio files (wav)
      - Manuscript material accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc64 and afc2017049_dc67, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/9)
      - Mgurmas from Moorang lama's notebook at Hirmal's house, Lippa transcribed in Sarnath by [unknown]: I, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/8)
      - [Mgurma transcripts], 1995-1996, afc2017049_dc07; Mgurma of Rigzin Dudol, Ga Rinpoche's mgurma, Negi Lama's mgurma, Nesang mgurma #5, Somang mgurma I, Somang mgurma II, Three sung-gur.; 11 text files (wpd, doc)
      - Negi Rinpoche song Chosen Dolma & Jamura Bagh, Yongchen Dolma, July 21-November 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Negi Rinpoche's mgurma (Kunu Lama Tenzin Gyaltsen) pages 7 and 8; Sol Deb page 13, sung Jamyang Choeling, also sung Pangaon, September-October 1995
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/10)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR009 (Side A); 1 sound cassette
      - Nuns of Kinnaur sing githang, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR004; 1 sound cassette
      - Pangaon Punjabi song, May 4, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR001; 1 sound cassette
      - R. Sankrityayan, Kinnauri Songs (Hindi), undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Rasham Lal, Kinnauri history in Kinnauri, folk songs, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/12)
      - September 30, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR117; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Shungsep/tsoklu, mgurma, April 15, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR003; 1 sound cassette
      - Shungsep Jetsun song (to be danced) in posession of her disciple, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/13)
      - [Shungsep Jetsun's prayer song; song lists], 1995-1996
        - Song transcripts; song lists, 1 folder; 2 photo prints (4x6) (Box-folder 1/14)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR100, SR102, SR101, SR099, SR104; 5 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Somang mgurma I & II, October 1995-November 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/15)
      - Song about friend (Kanam nuns), 1996
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/16)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR007 (Side A); 1 sound cassette
      - Song of Buddha Shakyamuni (Panwi) (Negi song attached), December 4, 1995
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/17)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR124, SR097, SR023 (Side B); 2 sound cassettes (microcassette); 1 sound cassette
      - Song of Kangyur Rinpoche (Tsering Lhamo), June 1996
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/18)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR008; 1 sound cassette
      - Song of Lippa, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/19)
      - Song of Lobon Rinpoche (Tokto), July 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/20)
      - Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (short Sonam Rekyi version, Ribba) (Negi song attached), September 17, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/21)
      - Song of Negi Lama (Jamyang Choeling nuns), September 17, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/22)
      - Song of Nyima Zangmo, or Tashi Gang Gompa (Tenzin Choeden, Pangoan), October 18, 1995
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/23)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR118, SR115, SR022, SR023 (Side A); 2 sound cassettes (microcassette); 2 sound cassettes
      - Song of Root Guru (Tsering Lhamo), October 1996
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/24)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR014 (Side B); 1 sound cassette
      - Song of Yulgyal Tulku (Yongchen Dolma, Panwi, Dec. '95) (Gathering Friends attached), December 3, 1995
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/25)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR097; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Song on Impermanence (Yongchen Dolma, Sarnath, (of Nichar)) (Suffering of Separation attached), January 27, 1996
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/26)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR043; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Songs transcripts], 1995-1996, afc2017049_dc07; Song of Buddha Shakyamuni, Song of Bure Monastery, Song about friends, Suffering of Separation (short version), Song of Root Guru (Kachen Lama), Song of Kangyur Rinpoche, Song of Lippa, Song of Lobon Rinpoche, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (Kanam version), Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (Ribba longer version), Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (Ribba short version), Song on Impermanence, Song about Negi Rinpoche, Song of Negi Lama, Tashi Gang Gompa, Song of Yulgyal Tulku.; 23 text files (wpd, doc)
      - [Songs in Tibetan], undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Suffering of Separation (New Land), October 2, 1995
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/27)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR062; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Sung-gur I, II, III sung and danced at Losar in Lippa by jomos and lamas, September 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/28)
      - Tsering Lhamo githang CD #3, undated, afc2017049_dc65; Tsering Lhamo, Song of Kangyur Rinpoche parts 1 and 2.; 2 audio files (wav)
      - Manuscript material accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc65, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/10)
      - Tsokla: Jigme Lingpa's, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/29)
      - Urgyen Negi, Ven., his father's mgurma (sung at Pangaon, spring 1996 by his niece, a nun), June 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/30)
    - Interviews
      - Ani Dolma/Lama Topgyali's mgurma explanation 1A, February 7, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/31)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR029; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - August 19, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR046; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Bhaba Ani, May 19, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR089, SR143; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Bogti, 1A, B, in Tokto, Asarang, July 8-9, 1996
        - Interview transcripts; newsclippings, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/32)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc08; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR058, SR059; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Chandra Mani, February 4-July 23, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/33)
      - Choegen Rinpoche (Tashi Jong) tape 1A, 1B, November 11, 1995
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/34)
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/35)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR119; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Chos Nyid Sangmo interview], October 18, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Chos Nyid Zangmo (Pangaon) 1A, 1B, 2A (Tenzim Choeden attached, page 10), October 18, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/36)
      - Chosem Dolma (Bari), Yangchen Dolma (Nichar), July 20-22, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/37)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc08; 1 text file (doc)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR051, SR054; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - December 15, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR125; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - December 27-28, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR134; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - December 28-29, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR131; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - December 28, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR132; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - December 29, 1995-April 2, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR141; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Ga Rimpoche (Clemantown, Dehra Dun) 1A, 1B, 2A, 2B, January 6, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/38)
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/3)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR135, SR137; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Geden Choeling (Kanam), May 12, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR009; 1 sound cassette